ACTWU's Department of Occupational Safety and Health Records 5619/015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Workers Compensation. Federal Standards II, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Workers Compensation. Federal Standards I, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  pre-1979
- Workers' Compensation. General [Folder 1 of 2], 1979-1996 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Workers' Compensation. General [Folder 2 of 2], 1979-1996 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- W.C. Harvard Project, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Workers' Compensation. IAIABC, 1989-1999 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Workers' Compensation. Lawsuits, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Workers' Compensation. Literature, 1978-1994 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Workers' Compensation. National Council on Compensation Insurance [Folder 1 of 2], 1981-1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Workers' Compensation. National Council on Compensation Insurance [Folder 2 of 2], 1981-1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Workers' Compensation. National Symposium, 1984-1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Workers' Compensation. Occupational Disease, 1980-1984 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Workers' Compensation. Product Liability, 1976-1986 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Workers' Compensation. Rehabilitation, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Workers' Compensation. U.S. National Commission on Workers' Compensation, 1972-1975 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Workers' Compensation. U.S. Interdepartmental Task Force Report, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Workers' Compensation. U.S. DOL Studies of O.D. [Folder 1 of 2], 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Workers' Compensation. U.S. DOL Studies of O.D. [Folder 2 of 2], 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Workers' Compensation. U.S. House Committee, 1979-1985 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Workers' Compensation. U.S. Senate Committee, 1977-1985 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Workers' Compensation. U.S. Senate Committee [Folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Workers' Compensation. U.S. Senate Committee [Folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Workers' Compensation. Workers' Compensation Research Institute, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Dyes & Finishes. ACTWU Conference, 1982-1990 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Dyes & Finishes. Benzidine [Folder 1 of 2], 1978-1985 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Dyes & Finishes. Benzidine [Folder 2 of 2], 1978-1985 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Dyes & Finishes. Bladder Cancer-Literature, 1938-1989 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Dyes & Finishes. Bladder Cancer-Screening Literature, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Dyes & Finishes. Canada, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Dyes & Finishes. Disperse Dyes, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Dyes & Finishes. Dye Carrier, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Dyes & Finishes. Dyeing Garments, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  Newspaper Clippings
- Dyes & Finishes. Dyes [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1990 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Dyes & Finishes. Dyes [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1990 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Dyes & Finishes. Dyes I-General, 1934-1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Dyes & Finishes. Dyes II-Literature, 1976-1997 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Dyes & Finishes. Dyes III-NIOSH Study, 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Dyes & Finishes. Dyes IV-Kingsley Kay Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Dyes & Finishes. Dyes V-Contact Printing, 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Dyes & Finishes. Dyes VI-Mortality Study, 1978-1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Dyes & Finishes. Dyes VIII-Educational Materials, 1978-1982 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Dyes & Finishes. Dyes IX-Health Hazard Alert, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Dyes & Finishes. Dyes X-Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Dyes and Finishes Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Dyes and Finishes Enforcement, 1980-1985 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Dyes and Finishes NIOSH Pamphlet, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Dyes and Finishes NTP Studies, 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Dyes and Finishes EPA, 1991-1994 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Dyes and Finishes EPA, 1978-1993 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Dyes and Finishes ACTWU Investigations, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Dyes and Finishes ACTWU Investigations, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Dyes and Finishes ACTWU Investigations Responses, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Dyes and Finishes NJ Health Department, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Dyes and Finishes Importation, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Dyes and Finishes Enzymes (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Safe Handling of Enzymes
- Dyes and Finishes Ecological and Toxicology Association of the Dyes Stuffs Manufacturing., IND., 1979-1991 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Dyes and Finishes Retardants (I) General, 1976-1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Dyes and Finishes Flame Retardants (II) Literature, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Dyes and Finishes Flame Retardants (III) Tris Literature, 1975-1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Dyes and Finishes Flame Retardants (IV) Tris CPSC and FFA, 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Dyes and Finishes Flame Retardants (V) Clippings, 1975-1979 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Dyes and Finishes General Clippings, 1974-1994 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Dyes and Finishes Finishing Bendix Study, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde, 1983-1990 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde #2, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde #2, 1980-1995 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde ACTWU Collective Bargaining, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde ACTWU Distribution, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Alternative Finishes, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  Ester Crosslinks: A Route to High Performance Nonformaldehyde Finishing of Cotton
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Advance Notice of Proposed Rule Making, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde American Apparel Manufacturers Association, 1979-1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Apparel Industries, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Video Tapes
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde ATMI, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Congressional Oversight, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Consumed Product Safety Commission, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Enforcement, 1990-1995 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde EPA 1987, 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Final Standard-OMB, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Labor Department ETS, 1981-1984 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Literature, 1984-1995 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde EPA, 1980-1989 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Institute, 1989-1994 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Monitoring Equipment, 1987-1993 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde NCI, 1980-1986 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde NIOSH Mortality Study 1984, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde NIOSH Mortality Study 1984, 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde NIOSH Mortality Study 1983, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Petition for ETS (1987- ) (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Petition for ETS, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Petition for Review Final STD, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Proposed STD, 1986-1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde proposed STD. Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Prosed STD. ILGWU, 1985-1992 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Prosed STD. Industry Testimony, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Proposed STD. UAW, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Sampling Devices, 1986-1994 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Dyes and Finishes Formaldehyde Substitutes, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Dyes and Finishes General, 1978-1995 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Dyes and Finishes Hunter College, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Dyes and Finishes Manufacturers, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Dyes and Finishes NIOSH Criteria Documents, 1980-1997 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Dyes and Finishes OSHA Enforcement, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Dyes and Finishes Paterson Health Department, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Dyes and Finishes Reactive Dyes, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  French
- Dyes and Finishes Substitution Dyes, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Dyes and Finishes UNC Study, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Dyes and Finishes United Kingdom, 1978-1985 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Absorbent Cotton Co., 1985-1991 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Advanced Glass Fibers, Inc., 1985-1999 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- OSH case Alleson's of Rochester, Inc, 1989-1993 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  Photographs
- OSH Case American Fashion, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- OSH Case American fashion, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- American felt and Filter, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- OSH case American Linen, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- OSH Case American London, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- OSH Case American Mills, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- OSH Case American Textiles, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- OSH Case American White Cross, 1980-1989 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- OSH Case Anomatic, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- OSH Case A and P Coat, Apron, and Linen, 1990-1993 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- OSH Case Armstrong, 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- OSH Case Arrow Co, 1985-1988 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- OSH Atwater, Inc, 1978-1989 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- OSH Case Beverly Enterprises, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- OSH Case Ribb Co, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- OSH Bibb Co. Roanoke Rapids NC Collective Bargaining 1978-1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Bleyer Ind. Inc. Mt. Union P.A., 1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Borden Chemical Co. Columbus, Ohio, 1978-1995 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Brand-Rex Co. Willimantic CT, 1992-1998 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Brooks Bros., Inc. New York, NY, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- OSH Case BTR Sealing Systems Maryville Tennessee, 1979-1998 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- OSH Case BTR Sealing Systems Maryville, Tennessee, 1979-1989 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Buffalo Batt and Felt Corp. Depew, NY, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Burlington Industries General, 1979-1990 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Butterick Pattern Altoona Pennsylvania, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Carville-National Leather, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Chipman-Union Inc, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Cluett Peabody Docket #90-3050, 1989-1992 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Cluett Peabody Co. Collective Bargaining, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Cluett Peabody, INC. Cedartown GA, 1983-1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Photos
- OSH Case Cliftex Mfg. New Bedford, MA, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Colecraft Manufacturing Co., Inc, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Colonial Tanning Gloversville NY, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Cone Mills Greensboro NC, 1980-1994 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Cone Mills General, 1985-1990 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- OSH case Cone Mills Corp. Pazzaz Mexico, 1983-1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Corbin, ltd. Ashland Kentucky, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Cordova Spinning Mills Cordova Alabama, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- OSHA Case Courtlands, N.A.,Ltd Lemoyne Alabama, 1978-1989 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Courtaulds, N.A. II, 1979-1989 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Courtaulds Mobile Alabama Monitoring Data, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- OSHA Case Craddock Terry Shoe Corp. Farmville, Virginia, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Cranston Print Works Ed Griffin Case, 1981-1987 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Cranston Print Works Company Webster, MA, 1984-1992 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Creative Foam Fenton, Mich., 1982 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Cyclops Inc. Downingtown Pennsylvania, 1981-1993 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- OSHA Case Divine Brothers Company Utica New York, 1976-1993 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Dupont General (Box 20, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Dupont General Clippings, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Dupont Corporation Deepwater, NJ, 1986-1989 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Dupont Corporation Gibbstown, New Jersey, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Dupont Corporation IBDW Convention 10/28/88, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Dupont Company Parkersburg West Virginia, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Dupont, Inc. Seaford, Delaware, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Dupont Company Waynesboro, Virginia, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Duro Finishing Corporation Fall River, Massachusetts, 1983-1988 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Duro textile Printers, Inc. Fall River Massachusetts, 1983-1989 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Dyescraftsmen Inc. Taunton Massachusetts, 1981-1989 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Echlin, Inc. EPE Company DIV. Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1984-1988 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- OSH Case EPE, Inc. Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Empire Dist. Inc. Atlanta Georgia, 1989-1991 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Ensign-Bickford II Docket # 79-0603 Simsbury, Connecticut, 1978-1984 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Ensign Bickford Company Avon, Connecticut, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Ensign-Bickford Simsbury, Connecticut 1984 Explosion, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Ensign-Bickford Training Case, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Excel IV, Inc. Clifton, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Fabricolor, Inc. Patterson, New Jersey, 1980-1994 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- OSH Case Fashion Tanning, Company Gloversville, New York, 1985-1992 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- OSH Case Fender Inst. Westerly, Rhode Island, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- OSH Case Fieldcrest, 1991-1995 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- OSH Case Fieldcrest Mills General, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- OSH Case Fieldcrest Mills Phoenix City, Alabama, 1987-2000 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Fieldcrest Columbus, Georgia, 1985-1995 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Case Fieldcrest Mills Feldale, Virginia, 1982-1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. OSHRC Docket #86-1638, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- M. Fine and Sons Mfg. Company New Albany, Ind, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Fingerhut St. Clouts, MN, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Fleetwood Shirt Company., Inc. Fleetwood, Pennsylvania, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Flexo-Transparent Inc., 1990 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Florsheim Shoes General, 1982-1995 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Foamex Corp. Cornellius, New York, 1986-1988 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Fruit of the Loom Crowley, LA, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Furtex Corporation Jackson Tennessee, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Galley and Lord Inc. (Swift Textile Div.) Erwin, North Carolina, 1977-1990 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Garden State Tanning Fleetwood, Pennsylvania, 1986-1988 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- GEAUGA Ind, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- OSHA Case Geauga Industries, Inc. Middlefield, Ohio`, 1977-1984 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Globe International Inc. Buffalo, New York, 1978-1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Gold Valet Inc., 1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Greenwood Mills, Lindale, Georgia, 1986-1993 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Guilford Mills, 1989-2003 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Gulf Fibers, Inc. Axis Alabama, 1990-1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Hanes Corp. Winston-Salem, N.C., 1980-1984 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Hanes Corp. Galax Virginia, 1982-1986 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- OSH Case hanes Corp. General, 1981-1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Harodite Finishing Company Taunton, Maine, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Harris Tipograph, North Bergen, New Jersey, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Hart, Scnaffner, and Marx Des Plaines, Illinois, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Hartmarx Corp. General, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Hartmarx Jaymar-Ruby General, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Whitevlle Apparel Corp., 1989 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- OSH Case C.F. Hathaway Company, 1984-1989 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Health-Tex, Inc. General, 1983-1987 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- OSH Case VF Corp./ Healthtex, Inc., 1986-1995 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Fidelity Industries, Inc. Wayne, New Jersey, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- OSHA Case Highland Yarn Mills High Point, North Carolina, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Case Docket no 92345, Highland Yard Mills, High Point, North Carolina, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Hoechst- Celanese Corporation General, 1988-1996 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- OSHA Case Celanese Fibers Company(Amcele Plant) Cumberland, Maryland, 1970-1979 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- OSHA Case Celanese Corporation (Celco Plant) Narrows, Virginia (Power Plant Explosion, 1973-1981 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Celanese Fibers Corporation (Methylene Chloride Study), 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- OSHA Case (Citation) Celanese Fibers Corporation Narrows, Virginia, 1972-1981 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Hoechst Celanese Collective Bargaining 92, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Hoechst-Celanese Corporation Collective Bargaining 1989, 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Hoechst-Celanese Corporation Rock Hill, South Carolina, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- OSH Hoechst-Celanese Corporation Narrows, Virginia, 1989-1995 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Hoechst-Celanese Corporation Narrows, Virginia, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- OSHA Case Celanese Corporation Rock Hill, South Carolina, 1975-1987 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Hollander Home Fashions, 1994-2001 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Homestead Industries. Claremont, New Hampshire, 1988-1994 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- OSH Case H.J. Horne and Sons Company Lawrence, Massachusetts, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- OSHA Case Huntsman Film Products Calhoun, Georgia, 1978-1992 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Industrial Powder Coatings Norwalk, Ohio, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Interstate Dye and Finishing Corporation Passaic, New Jersey, 1983-1994 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Jacob Brothers, South Hackensack, New Jersey, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Johnson and Johnson ESDP New Brunswick, New Jersey, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Johnson and Johnson Ethion Bridgewater, New York, 1981-1988 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Johnson and Johnson General (Box 24, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Johnson and Johnson Mexico, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Juno Lighting Inc., 1989-2000 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Justin Boot Company Fort Worth, Texas, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- OSH Case J-Wood Incorporated Milroy, Pennsylvania 17063, 1988-1990 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- OSH Case K-Mart, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- OSH Case K-Mart Negotiations 1995 Greensboro, North Carolina, 1992-1995 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- OSH Case K-Mart Negotiations Greensboro, North Carolina, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Kalkstein Silk Mills, Inc. Paterson, New Jersey, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Karg Brothers Finishing Corporation Johnstown, New York, 1986-1993 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Kawneer Company, Inc. Franklin Indiana, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Kenyon Piece Dye Works, Kenyon, Rhode Island, 1982-1989 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Kleen Brite Labs. Inc. General, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Kleen Brite Labs, Inc. Rochester, New York, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- OSH Case Kleen Test Prod. Inc. Brown Deer, Wisconsin (Box 24, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Klote International Corporation, Maryville, TN, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Kraft Hat Mfg. Bronx, New York, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- OSH Case Kuss Corporation Findlay, Ohio, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Lehigh Valley Throwing Mill, Fountain Hill, Pennsylvania, 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- OSH Case The Leshner Corporation, Hamilton, Ohio, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Levi Strauss 1988 Corporate H and S Manual (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Levi Strauss and Company Clippings, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- OSH Case Levi Strauss General, 1986-1998 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Levi Strauss Collective Bargaining, 1987-1995 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Levi Strauss Collective Bargaining National Agreement, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Levi Strauss and Company Ergonomic, 1985-1994 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Levi Strauss Evaluation, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Levi Strauss and Company Arkansas, 1985-1994 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Levi Strauss and Company El Paso, Texas, 1986-1989 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Levi Strauss Texas, 1986-1999 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Levi Strauss Mississippi, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Levi Strauss and Company Valdosta, Georgia, 1983-1993 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Levi Strauss SAFE Programs, 1994-1996 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Levi Strauss Safety and Health Steering Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Lincoln Brass Works Incorporated, Jacksboro, Tennessee, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Lindale Manufacturing (subs. Greenwood Mills) Lindale, Georgia, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Lindale Manufacturing Company, 1983-1989 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Londontown Corporation General, 1984-1990 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Lockheed Pomona, California, 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- OSH Case Lord West, Woodside, New York, 1988-1990 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Louisville Manufacturing Company General, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Madison Polymeric Eng. Meridan Connecticut, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- OSH Case Manchester Knitted Fashions. Inc, Manchester, New Hampshire, 1980-1988 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Manhattan Ind. Inc. Winnsboro, South Carolina, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Manner Textile Processing Haledon, New Jersey, 1983-1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Maryland Ribbon Company, Hagerstown, Maryland, 1979-1987 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- OSH Case C.H. Masland Carpet Atmore, Alabama, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- OSHA Case Masland Carpet, Carlisle, Pennsylvania, 1979-1993 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Masland Industries, Sidney, Ohio, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- OSH Case masland Corporation (subs. Lear Corporation) Lewistown, Pennsylvania, 1989-1995 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Masland Carpet, Lewistown, Pennsylvania, 1983-1993 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Meiwa Manufacturing Company, Charlotte, North Carolina, 1980-1988 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Melton Shirt Company, Batavia, New York, 1980-1988 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Meramic Industries, 1988-1991 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Metal Cladding, Inc. North Tonawanda, New York, 1988-1993 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Microfibers Incorporated Pawticket, Rhode Island, 1988-1999 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Microfibres, Incorporated, 1994-1997 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Milligan and Higgins, Johnstown, New York, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Milliken, Inc. Spartanburg, South Carolina, 1979-1981 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Monroe Manufacturing Company Monroe, Louisiana, 1993-1997 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Monroe Manufacturing Docket number 93-2874/93-2843, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Monroe Manufacturing Inc. Docket number 92-3082, 5 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Monterey Mills Inc. Cowan Tennessee, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Napp Chemicals, Inc. Lodi, New Jersey, 1986-1995 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Napp Tech General, 1994-1997 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Napp Tech Clippings, 1988-1995 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- OSH Case National Leather Corporation, Johnstown, New York, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- OSH Case New London Textile Inc., 1988 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- OSH Case North Bergen Piece Dye Works Incorporated, North Bergen, New Jersey, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Nugmeg Corp. (sub VECorp) Tampa Florida, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Ohio City Manufacturing, Ohio City, Ohio, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Omnicology Inc. Gloversville, New York, 1986-1988 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- OSHA Case Oneita Knitting Mills, Inc. Andrews, South Carolina, 1975-1986 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- OSHA Case Oneita Mills, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 17)